Bridge Line Historical Society; Collection mss129
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Administrative and Subject Files, 1907-1994; 1; 4.78 cubic ft.
  - New York Central Railroad: Conductor's Cash Fare Receipts, Undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - New York Central Railroad: Non-transferable Conductor's Interline Train Tickets, Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - New York Central Railroad: Transfer Check Northward, Undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - New York Central Railroad Company: Manual of Instructions to Passenger Conductors, Helper Conductors, Assistant Conductors and Ticket Collectors, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - New York Central Railroad Company: Memorandum "Family" Step-Up Table No. 8, Undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - New York Central System: New York Central Railroad Lines East District, List of Stations and Station Numbers, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - New York Central System: Passenger Wheel Report, Undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - New York Power and Light Corporation Distribution: Port Henry District, Delaware and Hudson Permit with Correspondence, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA0010032
  - Penn Central Conductors Tariff 43, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Penn Central Non-transferrable Conductor's System Train Ticket, Undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Pins: "UTU Hearts New York" and "Ride the Turbo! Amtrack 1976", Undated (Oversized 1)
  - Plate with Inscription "The Empire State Express", Undated (Oversized 1)
  - President's Letters to Employees, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Proposed Increase in Passenger Speeds: Schenectady to Whitehall and Whitehall to Rouses Point, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000918
  - Proposed Rehabilitation to Freight Main Line: Bangor ME to Sunbury, PA, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000921
  - Pullman Company Tea Towel, Undated (Oversized 1)
  - Railroad Calendar, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Railway Passenger Travel 1825-1880, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Remittance Envelope for National Commerical Bank and Trust Company, Undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Sketch of Spring Switch Layout with Note from February 4, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Sleeping Car Envelope Forms, Undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Sleeper Coach and Dining Car Envelopes, Undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Steam Railroad Calendar, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Steam Railroad Calendar, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Steam Railroad Calendar, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Steam Railroad Calendar, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Steam Railroad Calendar, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Stub to be Retailed by Conductor, Undated (Box 4, Folder 30)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000159
  - 1985 Surfacing Gang Schedule (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Ticket for Coach Passengers, Undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000161
  - Trains: The Magazine of Railroading, 1975 June (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Trains: The Magazine of Railroading, 1975 October (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Trainman News: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Transfer Tickets, Punch Slips and Conductors' Memorandum, Undated (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Trunk Line-Central Passenger Tariff Bureau: Fares and Arrangements Governing Transportation of Blind Persons, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000149
  - Trunk Line-Central Passenger Tariff Bureau: Local, Interdivision and Joint Tariff O.S. No. 11, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000147
  - Work-Day Stub Retained by Engineer, Undated (Box 4, Folder 39)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000158
  - Work Equipment Listing, 1926-1974 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000178
  - Work Equipment Program Purchases, 1943-1968 (Oversized 2)
  - Work Equipment Showing Descriptions and Assigned Numbers (1 of 2), 1945; 1958-1959; 1968 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000180
  - Work Equipment Showing Descriptions and Assigned Numbers (2 of 2), 1948-1950; 1957-1958; 1961 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Work Equipment Showing Cost, Assigned Numbers and Description (1 of 2), 1958-1959; 1967-1968; 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000181
  - Work Equipment Showing Cost, Assigned Numbers and Description (2 of 2), 1963; 1966-1969; 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Maps, Blueprints, and Drawings, 1870-2004; 2; 613 items
  This series is comprised of maps, blueprints, and drawings that are related to the train stations affiliated with the Delaware and Hudson Line. Most of the maps within this series are reproductions.
  - #1: Proposed Branch from Moreau Station to South Glens Falls and Spur to Bakers Falls, Abandoned - See Final Location #2: First Location of South Glens Falls Branch and Spur to Bakers Falls #3: Sketch, Marked as not Accurate Shows Proposed Electric Railroad Route (Partial; Paralleling So. Glens Falls Branch), 1901 (Map-tube 103)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000104; Other Identification Number: 709-2497
  - Afton, NY Depot Grounds: Alignment and Property Ownerships, Plus Profile (Two Sheets in Set), Undated (Map-tube 108)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000078; Other Identification Number: 527-4946
  - Automatic Switch Heaters Installed at "DE" Cabin, 1955 (Map-tube 338)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001150
  - Ballston, NY Trackage, Undated (Map-tube 69)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000071; Other Identification Number: 708-1713
  - Bill of Material for Sanitary Closet and Septic Tank for Railroad with Schematic (Reproduction of 1919 Record), Undated (Map-tube 316)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001111
  - Blueprint of New Engine House in Menands, Undated (Map-tube 267)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001304; Other Identification Number: 36-941
  - Blueprint of Train Tracks in Beekmantown, NY, Undated (Map-tube 91)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000074; Other Identification Number: ?-34568
  - Bridge 1: Penn Division, Rolled Beam Bridge of Plymouth Junction (PA), 1890 (Map-tube 109)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000075; Other Identification Number: 66-27278
  - Bridge No. 26, Penn Division, 1887 (Map-tube 71)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000032; Other Identification Number: 66-27245
  - Bridge Number 36, Penna. Division, 1890 (Map-tube 112)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000095; Other Identification Number: 66-27285
  - Bridges 44A, 53, 55, Penn Division (five drawings); One Marked "Reinforcing of Old Bridge 53, To be Used at Anthracite Park, Penn Div" (Reproductions of 1900's Maps), Undated (Map-tube 16)
    Other Identification Number: 66-27280
  - Cable Post Base Comp. First Made for N.Y.C. and St. L. (Reproduction of 1930 Map), Undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - [Castleton Branch], Undated (Map-tube 68)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000040
  - Chateauguay Railroad Profile of Chateauguay Valley Preliminary from Lyon Mountain to Twin Pond (Reproduction of 1902 Map), Undated (Map-tube 257)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001323; Other Identification Number: 16-69
  - Copy of Plans - Tentative Review - Public Service Commission for Relocation of Main Line, Whitehall, NY (Set of 4), 1931 (Map-tube 83)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000044; Other Identification Number 467-35356
  - Cross-sections, Albany to Green Island Scheme (10 sheets), 1922 (Map-tube 12)
  - D&H Company: Penn Division, Elevations of Proposed Yardmasters Office, Carbondale, PA (scheme 1), Undated (Map-tube 41)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000036; Other Identification Number: 544-28451-55
  - D&H Company: Penn Division, Elevations of Proposed Yardmasters Office, Carbondale, PA (scheme 2), Undated (Map-tube 44)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000047
  - D&H Company: Plan and Profile of Tracks with Proposed Siding, Between State Street and Edison Avenue (Schenectady), Undated (Map-tube 80)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000049; Other Identification Number: 12-3345
  - D&H Company: Susquehanna Division, Map Showing New Alignment of D&H Company's Tracks West of NYC & HR RR Bridge (Reproduction of 1905 Map), Undated (Map-tube 79)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000033; Other Identification Number: 12-3347
  - D&H Company: Track Profile, Locations Unknown, Undated (Map-tube 99)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000050
  - D&H Pennsylvania: (Rolled steel) Bridge Diagram, Bridge 52, Undated (Map-tube 42)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000057
  - D&H Station: Round Lake, NY (Architectural Drawings), Undated (Map-tube 47)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000043; Other Identification Number: 14-V50423
  - D&H Station: Plan of Dining and Lunch Rooms, Whitehall N.Y., Undated (Map-tube 50)
    Other Identification Number: G27-V51139
  - Delaware & Hudson Co, Pennsylvania Division: Profile [of] Nineveh Branch, 1923 (Map-tube 95)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000073; Other Identification Number: 55-35
  - Delaware & Hudson Co. Susquehanna Division: Frog and Switch for International Bonded Warehouse Co., So. Albany, NY, 1910 (Map-tube 8)
  - Delaware & Hudson Co., Penn Division: Proposed Change of Highway at Lockwood Crossing So., Nineveh, NY (Colesville County, Broome County), Estimates, Working Sketches, Undated (Map-tube 105)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000038; Other Identification Number: 12-4529
  - Delaware & Hudson Co.: Eastern Portion of U.S., Showing Principal RR Lines and Steamship Ports (Reproduction of 1918 Map), Undated (Map-tube 73)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000052; Other Identification Number: 522-28406
  - Delaware & Hudson Co.: Saratoga, Champlain, Pennsylvania, Susquehanna Divisions; Shows Rail Lines, Highways, Stations (entire railroad), 1933 (Map-tube 45)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000045; Other Identification Number: 538-36067
  - Delaware & Hudson Company Susquehanna Division: New Station at Sidney, NY (Reproduction of 1912 Map) (15 items), Undated (Map-tube 17)
  - Delaware & Hudson Company: 80000 lb. Hopper Gondola (Erecting Drawing), 1901 (Map-tube 25)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA-000114
  - Delaware & Hudson Company: Air Brake Application to Hopper Gondola of 80000 lb. Capacity, 1901 (Map-tube 24)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA-000113
  - Delaware & Hudson Company: Air Brake Forgings for 80000 lb. Capacity Hopper Gondola, 1901 (Map-tube 22)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA-000111
  - Delaware & Hudson Company: Air Brake Forgings for Hopper Gondola of 80000 lb. Capacity, 1901 (Map-tube 26)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA-000115
  - Delaware & Hudson Company: Center Truss Rod Strut, 1901 (Map-tube 32)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA-000121
  - Delaware & Hudson Company: Details for Hopper Gondola of 80000 lb. Capacity, 1901 (Map-tube 23)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA-000112
  - Delaware & Hudson Company: Details for Truck for Car of 80000 lb. Capacity for 40-ton 2-Bay Hopper Gondola, 1901 (Map-tube 21)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA-000110
  - Delaware & Hudson Company: Step, 1901 (Map-tube 29)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA-000118
  - Delaware & Hudson Company: The Butler Draw Bar Attachment; Application of Attachment #99, 1901 (Map-tube 27)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA-000116
  - Delaware & Hudson Company: Truss Rod Strut, 1901 (Map-tube 28)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA-000117
  - Delaware & Hudson Company: Truss Rod Strut, 1901 (Map-tube 31)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA-000120
  - Delaware & Hudson Company: Truss Rod Washer, 1901 (Map-tube 30)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA-000119
  - Delaware & Hudson: Profile of High Level Line, Scheme A; Covers Waterford Junction to North Albany ca 1921, proposed main line relocation box (Map-tube 38)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000042
  - Delaware & Hudson: Profile of Line from Fort Edward to Sandy Hill, Undated (Map-tube 46)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000046; Other Identification Number: 12-2510
  - Delaware and Hudson Co. Champlain Division: Express Building for the National Express Company, Saranac Lake, N.Y. (Reproduction of 1915 Map), Undated (Map-tube 1)
    Other Identification Number: 238-26333
  - Delaware and Hudson Co. Saratoga Division: Lake George Branch, Fort Edward to Mile Post 63 (Reproduction of 1910 Map), Undated (Map-tube 58)
  - Delaware and Hudson Co. Saratoga Division: Lake George Branch, Mile Post 62 to Lake George (Reproduction of 1910 Map), Undated (Map-tube 59)
  - Delaware and Hudson Co., Champlain Division: Building to be Erected at Shelburne Harbor, VT. For Champlain Transportation Company, Map 20268 (Reproduction of 1910 Map), Undated (Map-tube 160)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001243
  - Delaware and Hudson Co., Champlain Division: Building to be Erected at Shelburne Harbor, VT. For Champlain Transportation Company, Map 20269 (Reproduction of 1910 Map), Undated (Map-tube 164)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001241
  - Delaware and Hudson Co., Freight House, Glens Falls, NY (Reproduction of 1902 Map), Undated (Map-tube 166)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001217
  - Delaware and Hudson Co., Pennsylvania Division, Signal Track Diagrams (Eight Sheets), Undated (Map-tube 146)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001200-BLA001207
  - Delaware and Hudson Co., Saratoga Division Additions as Proposed at Freight Station Green Island, N.Y.; Plans 23344-23352 (8 Sheets)(Reproduction of 1912 Map), Undated (Map-tube 144)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001347-BLA001405
  - Delaware and Hudson Co., Saratoga Division Additions as Proposed at Freight Station Green Island, N.Y.; Plans 23577-23584 (7 Sheets) (Reproduction of 1912 Map), Undated (Map-tube 148)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Numbers: BLA001406-BLA001413
  - Delaware and Hudson Co., Susquehanna Division: Val. Sec 4. Proposed Rearrangement of Car Shops at Oneonta, NY, 1927 (Map-tube 159)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001192
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Baggage Car, Arch Type Roof with Steel Underframe (Reproduction of 1925 Map), Undated (Map-tube 270)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001286; Other Identification Number: R-30156
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Blueprint for Smoker Car with Turtle-Back Roof (Reproduction of 1925 Map), Undated (Map-tube 227)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001287; Other Identification Number: R30075
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Blueprint of Coach Car (Reproduction of 1926 Map), Undated (Map-tube 259)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001290; Other Identification Number: R-30555
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Boston and Maine and Hudson Valley Railway Tracks at Thomson, NY (Reproduction of 1911 Map), Undated (Map-tube 250)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000556A
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Champlain Division Maps, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000949
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Champlain Division, Additions to Freight Station in Plattsburgh, NY (Reproduction of 1912 Map), Undated (Map-tube 272)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001296-BLA001301
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Champlain Division; Details of Bar Rack for Section Tool Houses (Reproduction of 1927 Map), Undated (Map-tube 330)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001105
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Champlain Division; Proposed New Sand House in Whitehall, NY (Reproduction of 1906 Map), Undated (Map-tube 413)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001361A-BLA001361C
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Champlain Division; Standard A.R.E.A. Portable Snow Fence (Reproduction of 1922 Map), Undated (Map-tube 333)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001106
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Coach Passenger, Plan and Elevation (Reproduction of 1921 Map), Undated (Map-tube 269)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001289
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Construction Chart, Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Crossing Watchmen Chart (Reproduction of 1919 and 1929 Map), Undated (Map-tube 262)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001093
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Floor Plan and Interior Arrangement for Caboose, Undated (Map-tube 456)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000853B
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Freight House North Creek, N.Y. (Reproduction of 1902 Map), Undated (Map-tube 192)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001218
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Freight House Saratoga, N.Y. (Reproduction 1902), Undated (Map-tube 191)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001216
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Freight House Watervliet, N.Y. (Reproduction of 1902 Map), Undated (Map-tube 186)
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Freight House, Schenectady NY (Reproduction of 1901 Map), Undated (Map-tube 406)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001365
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Freight House, Schenectady NY (Reproduction of 1902 Map), Undated (Map-tube 424)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001366
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Freighthouse-Cobleskill (Reproduction of 1900 Map), Undated (Map-tube 358)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001169; Other Identification Number: 612-7123
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: General Arrangement of Train Cars (Reproduction of 1967 Map), Undated (Map-tube 458)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000850A
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: House, Iron in Green Island (Reproduction of 1906 Map), Undated (Map-tube 282)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001322
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Lettering for Produce Cars in Milk Service (Reproduction of 1923 Map), Undated (Map-tube 271)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000847
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Map of Junctions from Rotterdam to Mechanicville (Sheet A-7), Undated (Map-tube 200)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001306
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Map of Junctions Near New York/Vermont State Lines (Sheet B-8), Undated (Map-tube 199)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001312
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Map of Junctions on the New York/Massachusetts/Vermont State Lines (Sheet B-7), Undated (Map-tube 211)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001311
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Map of Junctions on the New York/Vermont State Lines (Sheet B-10), Undated (Map-tube 216)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001315
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Map of Junctions on the United States/Canadian Border (Sheet B-13), Undated (Map-tube 210)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001318
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Map of Junctions the New York/ Vermont State Lines (Sheet B-12), Undated (Map-tube 248)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001317
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Map of Lake Stations Near New York/Vermont State Lines (Sheet 9-B), Undated (Map-tube 205)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001313
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Map of Train Stops from Castleton to Mt. Holly (Sheet C-9), Undated (Map-tube 212)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001314
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Map of Train Stops from Knox Siding to Kenwood Junction (Sheet A-6), Undated (Map-tube 204)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001305
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Map of Train Stops from Loon Lake to Lake Placid (Sheet A-11), Undated (Map-tube 213)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001209
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Map of Train Stops from Twin Ponds to Morrisonville, Undated (Map-tube 207)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001310
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Map of Train Stops from Warrensburg to North Creek (Sheet 9-A), Undated (Map-tube 206)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: 001308
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Map of Train Stops in Saratoga County (Sheet A8), Undated (Map-tube 220)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001307
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Map of Train Stops on the New York/Vermont State Lines (Sheet B-11), Undated (Map-tube 221)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001316
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Outline Map of System (Reproduction of 1923 Map), Undated (Map-tube 249)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001303; Other Identification Number: 31-31496
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Passenger and Baggage Car with Arch Type Roof with Steel Underframe (Reproduction of 1925 Map), Undated (Map-tube 275)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001288; Other Identification Number: R-31067
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Pennsylvania Division, 2nd Floor and Roof Plan for Proposed Yardmaster's Office in Carbondale, PA (Reproduction of 1918 Map), Undated (Map-tube 391)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001378-BLA001378A
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Pennsylvania Division, Plan Showing Proposed Layout for Combination Camp Coach (Reproduction of 1919 Map), Undated (Map-tube 263)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001119
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Pennsylvania Division; Elevations for Proposed Yardmaster's Office in Carbondale, PA (Reproduction of 1918 Map), Undated (Map-tube 396)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001376-BLA001376A
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Pennsylvania Division; Foundation and 1st Floor Plan for Proposed Yardmaster's Office in Carbondale, PA (Reproduction of 1918 Map), Undated (Map-tube 393)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001379-BLA001379A
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Pennsylvania Division; Map Showing Tracks Serving Hudson Coal Company at Loree Breaker Formerly Plymouth No. 5 (Reproduction of 1955 Map), Undated (Map-tube 554)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000898
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Pennsylvania Division; Plan Showing Proposed Alterations to Interior of Passenger Station at Scranton, PA (Reproduction of 1917 Map), Undated (Map-tube 415)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001394
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Pennsylvania Division; Sections and Details for Proposed Yardmasters' Office in Carbondale, PA (Reproduction of 1918 Map), Undated (Map-tube 399)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001377
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Proposed Bituminous Roadway and Street Crossing (Reproduction of 1926 Map), Undated (Map-tube 320)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001098
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Proposed Bituminous Roadway and Street Crossings (Reproduction of 1926 Map), Undated (Map-tube 339)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001099
  - Delaware and Hudson Company: Proposed Changes and Alterations to the Troy Union Station (Reproductions of 1909 Map) (12 sheets), Undated (Map-tube 177)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001247